<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AIS-catcher</string>
    <string name="license_text"><![CDATA[
AIS-catcher for Android uses the following libraries:<P><P>
<b>* libusb-1.0.26</<b><P>
<a href="https://github.com/libusb/libusb">https://github.com/libusb/libusb</a><P>
libusb is a library for USB device access from Linux, macOS, Windows, OpenBSD/NetBSD, Haiku and Solaris userspace. It is written in C (Haiku backend in C++) and licensed under the GNU Lesser General Public License version 2.1 or, at your option, any later version (see COPYING).<P>
<P>
<b>* rtl-sdr</<b><P>
<a href="https://github.com/osmocom/rtl-sdr">https://github.com/osmocom/rtl-sdr</a>
Turns your Realtek RTL2832 based DVB dongle into a SDR receiver. Licensed under the GPL-2.0 license.
Modified for Android to open devices with file descriptors: https://github.com/jvde-github/rtl-sdr<P>
<P>
<b>* airspyhf</<b><P>
<a href="https://github.com/airspy/airspyhf">https://github.com/airspy/airspyhf</a><P>
This repository contains host software (Linux/Windows) for Airspy HF+, a high performance software defined radio for the HF and VHF bands. Licensed under the BSD-3-Clause license.<P>
Modified for Android to open devices with file descriptors: https://github.com/jvde-github/airspyhf<P>
<P>
<b>* airspyone_host</<b><P>
<a href="https://github.com/airspy/airspyone_host">https://github.com/airspy/airspyone_host</a><P>
AirSpy usemode driver and associated tools<P>
https://github.com/jvde-github/airspyone_host<P>
<P>
<b>* AIS-catcher</<b><P>
<a href="https://github.com/jvde-github/AIS-catcher">https://github.com/jvde-github/AIS-catcher</a><P>
AIS receiver for RTL SDR dongles, Airspy R2, Airspy Mini, Airspy HF+, HackRF and SDRplay. Licensed under the GPGL v3.0 license.<P>
]]></string>

    <string name="disclaimer_text"><![CDATA[
<i>AIS-catcher for Android</i> is created for research and educational purposes under the GPL license.<P>
This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.<P>
This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.
<P>
You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program.  If not, see <a href="https://www.gnu.org/licenses/">https://www.gnu.org/licenses/</a>.
<P>
It is a hobby project and not tested and designed for reliability and correctness. You can play with the software but it is the user responsibility to use it prudently.
So, <b>DO NOT rely upon this software</b> in any way including for navigation and/or safety of life or property purposes.<p>
There are variations in the legislation concerning radio reception in the different administrations around the world.
It is your responsibility to determine whether or not your local administration permits the reception and handling of AIS messages from ships and you can have this App on your phone.
It is specifically forbidden to use this software for any illegal purpose whatsoever. It is intended <b>for use only</b> in those regions where such use <b>is permitted</b>.<p>
]]></string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
</resources>
